## **Matthew McDaid**

Galway House, Radnor Street, London, EC1V 3SL +447553752876, matthewmcdaid1@hotmail.com, www.linkedin.com/in/matthewpmcdaid, https://github.com/Mcdaid101

			_
PR	OF	ш	Æ

English and History graduate of NUI Galway and Certificate in Computing graduate of National College of Ireland. I have several years' experience in customer service, retail and logistical based roles and two years' experience in the pharmaceutical manufacturing industry as a production operator. I am a student at the UCD Professional Academy and the Code Institute studying a Professional Diploma in Full-Stack Software Development where I am hoping to gain a future career in the computing industry. I am also a qualified English as a foreign language teacher with my degree awarded by the TEFL institute. Currently searching for a position in London.

## **EDUCATION**

Sep 2022 — Present

Part time (Weekends) Professional Diploma in Full-Stack Development, The Code Institute.

Modules studied: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python and SQL.

May 2022 — Aug 2022

Certificate in Computing (Level 8), National College of Ireland, Dublin

Grade: 2:1 (Hons)

Modules studied: Computer Architecture, Operating Systems and Networks. Introduction to Databases.

Sep 2017 — May 2020

BA in History and English, National University of Ireland, Galway

Grade: 2:2

Modules studied: English Literature, Romanticism, Creative Writing, Warfare, Pre-War Germany, Irish History.

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Aug 2022 — Dec 2022

Customer Service Agent, Electric Ireland

- · Provided customers with quality assistance through phone calls.
- · Implemented product and system knowledge to problem solve for customers.
- · Taking payments and setting up direct debits.

Mar 2022 — Aug 2022

Delivery Van Driver, Clare Distribution Services

- Delivered groceries to customers for a local supermarket chain.
- · Keeping track of customers faulty goods and refunding them where necessary
- · Maintaining the upkeep of the company van.

Aug 2021 — Mar 2022

Production Operator, AbbVie

- · Inspected and produced cosmetic products for CoolSculpting.
- · Monitored quality control of products.
- · Work efficiently to meet target deadlines.

Oct 2020 — Aug 2021

Production Operator, Medtronic

- Producing catheters on a production line.
- Inspecting each product was up to the standard of the quality department.
- Maintained a clean workspace.

June 2017 — May 2019

Sales Assistant, Spar - Letterkenny & Galway

- Ensured high levels of customer satisfaction.
- Processed cash and card transactions.
- · Monitored and replenished stock levels.

SKILLS	Communication Problem Solving	Programming Diligent
ACHIEVEMENTS	Full Driving License	
	Manual Handling	
	Safe Pass Certificate	

REFERENCES

References available upon request.